Pratyaksa

Email: praty.axa@gmail.com Phone: +62 813 1646 2152 Website: http://aksasite.me

ABOUT

Database engineer with 5+ years of experience and proven knowledge of database design and full stack development. Skilled in SQL and providing logical solutions to high-level backend and data issues. Currently learning SPA with React. Let's work together!

SKILLS

- MySQL
- PostgreSQL
- React
- NodeJS
- Single-Page Application
- Python
- PHP

- Django
- Laravel
- Postman
- Git
- Holistics.io
- Metabase

EXPERIENCES

J Passport (Singaporean O2O for Japanese Brands) - Data Engineer

MAY 2018 - SEP 2021

- Created admin pages for financial reports.
- Migrated sales data in massive feature-merging projects.
- Led a project to refund points of users who were affected by Covid-19 lockdown.
- Supported sales team with data ETL and technical expertise.
- Spearheaded automation of complex queries in order to simplify data flow, lower potential bug risks, and improve system performance.
- Beta testing.
- Provided customer service via email and Facebook chat.

PT Kreasi Sejahtera Teknologi - Data Analyst

SEP 2017 - FEB 2018

- Improved quality of data by standardizing and removing duplicate records.
- Managed five data entry people by scheduling tasks and daily reports.
- Efficient use of Excel and MySQL tools resulted in the best performing data entry team in the
 office.

Freelance and Other Works

JAN 2015 - PRESENT

Migrated data for the Indonesian National Archives' (ANRI) new website.

EDUCATION